<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20160614</CreaDate><CreaTime>09013600</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>FGDC CSDGM Metadata</ArcGISstyle><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><DataProperties><itemProps><itemName Sync="TRUE">ACS_2010_5yr_Median_HH_Income</itemName><imsContentType Sync="TRUE">002</imsContentType><itemSize Sync="TRUE">0.038</itemSize><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\159.83.112.39\gis01$\members\Demography\2010\Source\2010 Median HH income\ACS_2010_5yr_Median_HH_Income.dbf</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation></itemProps></DataProperties><SyncDate>20160713</SyncDate><SyncTime>11000200</SyncTime><ModDate>20160713</ModDate><ModTime>11000200</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>FGDC</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.2.2.3552</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="FALSE">2010 Median Household Income by Census Tract</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd value="011" Sync="TRUE"/></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="003" Sync="TRUE"></SpatRepTypCd></spatRpType><idPurp>2010 Median Household Income in the past 12 months (inflation-adjusted dollars) in Los Angeles County by 2010 Census Tracts.</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Household Income:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The sum of the income of all people 15 years and older living in the household. A household includes related family members and all the unrelated people, if any, such as lodgers, foster children, wards, or employees who share the housing unit. A person living alone in a housing unit, or a group of unrelated people sharing a housing unit, is also counted as a household.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Median: &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The point that divides the household income distribution into halves, one-half with income above the median and the other with income below the median. The median is based on the income distribution of all households, including those with no income. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;2010 Census Tract: &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;There are 3 different version&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;s&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;of 2010 Census Tract Boundary with slight change. This data is based on the 1st version of 2010 Census Tract. For further information, please refer to the file locate&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;d&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;at the eGIS Member Network Shared Drive Demography folder:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;'\Demography\Notice on Census Tract Update in 2012\Notice1 Census Tract Update in 2012.docx'&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Five-Year estimate:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The ACS produces period estimate of socioeconomic characteristics. It is designed to provide estimates describing the average characteristics of an area over a specific time period. In the case of 2010 and 2011 ACS 5-YR estimate, the period covers January 2006 through December 2010 and January 2007 through December 2011, respectively..&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P STYLE="margin:0 0 7 0;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;For further information, refer to the ACS handbook http://census.gov/content/dam/Census/library/publications/2008/acs/ACSGeneralHandbook.pdf&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>
Census Bureau's Population Estimates Program that produces and disseminates the official estimates of the population for the nation, states, counties, cities and towns and estimates of housing units for states and counties.</idCredit><searchKeys><keyword>Income</keyword><keyword>Household</keyword><keyword>Median Household Income</keyword><keyword>Census Tract</keyword></searchKeys><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;1. Terms of Use Introduction. Thank you for visiting the Los Angeles County GIS Data Portal (“Website”). This Website is operated by the County of Los Angeles (“LACO”, “County”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). The County makes a variety of datasets (“Data”) available for use and/or download on this Website. We ask that you carefully review these Terms of Use and all documents referenced in or linked from these Terms of Use (collectively, “Terms of Use”) before using our Website.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;2. License. Subject to these Terms of Use, you are granted a license to copy, publish, distribute and/or transmit the Data, to adapt the Data and to exploit the Data for commercial and/or personal use (collectively, “License”). No ownership interest in the Data is bestowed on you pursuant to these Terms of Use or the License. The License will be automatically voided and terminated without notice to you if you violate these Terms of Use. The License does not grant you any right to use the Data in any way that suggests County’s endorsement of your use.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;3. No Warranties. We provide the Website and Data to you on an “as is” basis without any warranties of any kind, whether express or implied. To the extent permissible under applicable law, we hereby disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to, warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement. Without limiting the foregoing, we do not make any representations or warranties that (a) the information, including but not limited to, the Data or other materials available on our Website will be error-free, (b) defects in our Data will be corrected, (c) our Website or its servers are free of viruses or other harmful components and/or (d) our Website will be secure, accessible continuously and without interruption. Further, we do not make any representations or warranties regarding the use, accuracy, reliability, and/or completeness of the information, including but not limited to the Data, or other materials available on our Website.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;4. Limitation of Liability. To the fullest extent permitted by law, we do not accept any liability for any conduct, acts or omissions occurring at this Website. Under no circumstances will we be liable to you for any direct, consequential, incidental or special damages, including any lost profits or loss of data, even if you claim to have notified us about such damages, or for any claims by any third parties. In no event will County be liable for any claim, including claims by third parties, for loss or damages arising from erroneous Data and/or errors contained on the Website. County’s total liability arising out of these Terms of Use is limited to $100.Indemnity.You agree to indemnify, defend and hold us harmless, at your own expense, from and against any liability, fees (including attorney’s fees) and/or costs arising out of or relating to your breach or violation of these Terms &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode value="eng" Sync="TRUE"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></mdLang><mdChar><CharSetCd value="004" Sync="TRUE"/></mdChar><distInfo><distFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">dBASE Table</formatName></distFormat><distTranOps><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.038</transSize></distTranOps></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="007" Sync="TRUE"/></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><eainfo><detailed Name="ACS_2010_5yr_Median_HH_Income"><enttyp><enttypl Sync="TRUE">ACS_2010_5yr_Median_HH_Income</enttypl><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Table</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">2346</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">OID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">OID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">OID</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">tract</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">tract</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">6</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">MedHIncm10</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">MedHIncm10</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">9</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">2</attscale></attr></detailed></eainfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20160713</mdDateSt></metadata>
